<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_version_string">App Version - %1$s</string>
    <string name="five_presc_received">%1$d prescriptions received</string>
    <string name="no_visit_created">No visit created</string>
    <string name="visit_intelehealth_for_more">For more visit our website intelehealth.org</string>
    <string name="aboutus_text">We are a tech-for-impact organisation : A team of engineers, clinicians, management and public health experts. We\'ve developed an innovative open source telemedicine platform connecting the last mile population.\n\nMission: We deliver quality healthcare where there is no doctor\n\nOur vision is Health for all.\n\nWe believe in the vision of universal health coverage - that you should be able to receive the health services you need, when and where you need them, without facing financial hardship. We believe in the vision of Universal Health Coverage - that you should be able to receive the health services you need, when and where you need them, without facing any financial hardship (WHO). But realizing this vision requires the collective efforts of an entire ecosystem. We aim to be a catalyst to empower existing health programs to deliver last-mile healthcare through well-designed user-centered telemedicine technology and implementation services. One thing that people don’t understand is that telemedicine is very empowering for women. For a woman living in rural India, health access is a privilege more than a right. Her access to health may be controlled by other people like her husband or in-laws. She has to rely on them for the permission, money, and transportation that she needs to get to a doctor in the nearby city. When I started working on Intelehealth, I was deeply touched by seeing how empowered women felt to be able to walk out of their house to a telemedicine clinic, talk to a doctor and get the care they needed on their own terms. I saw a woman beaten black and blue by her husband, whose in-laws would not give her any money to treat her injuries. The local health worker with the help of a remote doctor was able to assess her injuries, she gave her medicines to manage her pain, ointments to treat the scratches on her body and most important a kind and caring ear to soothe her soul. I met a woman whose husband refused to use any form of birth control and who wanted to speak with a doctor to understand what family planning options she could use. She discussed over teleconsultation various options and ultimately chose an IUD, which the local nurse was able to insert. I resonated deeply with the stories of these women. As a woman who has experienced abuse, I cannot express what it means to have this one thing - the ability to care for your own body - be in your control. I continue to be motivated by the power of telemedicine in creating easily accessible, safe spaces for women to get the care they rightfully deserve.\n\nNeha Verma\nCEO and Co-Founder, Intelehealth</string>
    <string name="add_patient">Add patients</string>

    <string name="enter_patient_s_body_measurement_details">Enter patient’s body measurement details</string>
    <string name="height_cm">Height (cm)</string>
    <string name="weight_kg">Weight (kg)</string>
    <string name="bmi_index_auto_calculated">BMI index(auto-calculated)</string>
    <string name="enter_the_patient_s_vitals">Enter the patient’s vitals</string>
    <string name="bp_sys">BP Sys</string>
    <string name="bp_dia">BP Dia</string>
    <string name="pulse_bpm">Pulse (bpm)</string>
    <string name="spo2">SpO2 (%)</string>
    <string name="respiratory_rate_breaths_min">Respiratory Rate (breaths/min)</string>
    <string name="temperature_f_new">Temperature (F)</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="ui2_physical_exam_summay_title">3/4. Physical examination summary</string>
    <string name="ui2_medical_hist_title_text">4/4. Medical history summary</string>
    <string name="sync_strated">"Sync started! "</string>
    <string name="priority_hint">Enable this in case visit is an Emergency.</string>
    <string name="mobile_no_not_provided">Mobile number not provided</string>
    <string name="please_wait_app_reset">Please wait a moment while the app is being reset.</string>
    <string name="please_wait_sync_progress">Please wait a moment while sync is in progress</string>
    <string name="invalid_mobile_no">Invalid mobile number</string>
    <string name="select_any_one">Select any one</string>
    <string name="select_one_or_more">Select one or more</string>
    <string name="sync_completed">Sync done!</string>
    <string name="unablet_get_the_doct_info_alert">Unable to get the doctor details!</string>
    <string name="video_call_req_sent">Request is sent to doctor for a video call</string>
    <string name="postal_code_6_dig_invalid_txt">Please enter 6 digit valid postal code</string>
    <string name="sanity_alert_title">Please wash/sanitize your hands</string>
    <string name="slider_desc">range slider</string>
    <string name="drag_tow_capture_range_from_0_to_100">Drag tow capture range from 0 to 100</string>
    <string name="ui2_no_information">No information</string>
    <string name="confirm_visit_reason">Confirm visit reason?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_the_patient_has_the_following_reasons_for_a_visit">Are you sure the patient has the following reasons for a visit?</string>
    <string name="check_up_reason">Check-up reason</string>
    <string name="know_more_txt">Know more</string>
    <string name="drag_anywhere_from_0_to_10">Drag anywhere from 0 to 10</string>
    <string name="follow_up_visits_not_found">Follow up visits not found!</string>
    <string name="enter_occupation_txt">Enter Occupation</string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="enter_your_relation_with_patient">Enter your relation with patient</string>
    <string name="end_visits">End Visits</string>
    <string name="empty_message_for_patinet_search_visit_screen">Use correct name or ID to search or add a new patient.</string>
    <string name="confirm_end_visit_reason">Close this visit?</string>
    <string name="confirm_end_visit_reason_message">Prescription should be shared before closing visit, are you sure you want to close the visit?</string>
    <string name="support_mobile_no_1">919503692181</string>
    <string name="help_whatsapp_string">Hello I’m  %1$s I need some assistance</string>
    <string name="update_app_protocol">Update app protocol!</string>
    <string name="please_enter_the_server_url_with_license_key_to_download_the_protocols">Please enter the server url with license key to download the protocols?</string>
    <string name="previously_scheduled_appointment_details">Previously scheduled appointment details</string>
    <string name="loading_slots">Loading slots...</string>
    <string name="alert_txt">Alert!</string>
    <string name="valid_dob_msg">Please select valid DOB!</string>
    <string name="all_patients_txt">All Patients</string>
    <string name="alert_label_txt">Alert!</string>
    <string name="describe_hint_txt">Describe...</string>
    <string name="duration_validation_txt">Please select the duration number</string>
    <string name="duration_type_validation_txt">Please select the duration type</string>
    <string name="select_date_hint">Select date</string>
    <string name="error_field_valid_village_required">Please enter the valid village name (Min 3 char)</string>
</resources>